<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>900Hasse</author>
	<version>1.0.1.0</version>
	<title>
        <en>REA22 Implements</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[The goal of this mod is to make the game feel more realistic and
customizing the vehicle for the task more rewarding.
The goal is to make the mod universal.
This mod supports multiplayer and dedicated servers.
No changes in XML is needed. Some data from XML is overwritten!

Pulling force for plows, cultivators, roller and sowingmachines is affected by ground type and state.
Balers, loading wagons and harvesters uses power based on fillspeed and density of material.

For example:
- Seeding directly into the stubble demands more power then seeding a cultivated field.
- Running a roller in a plowed field demands more power then a seedad field.
- Harvesting higher yeild demands more power then a low yeilding field.
- Lighter materials demands less power then heavy, baling hay is easier then grass.

The force applied to pulled tools is now applied on the correct place.
- Left or right side can get less or more force applied deending in the ground type and state on each side.
- Force is also applied from the sides to make implements more prone to follow their own path.

1.0.1.0
- Harvesters for sugerbeets and potatos no longer get to much power applied.
- If width of implement was changed groundstate node could cause errors, this is fixed.
]]>
</en>
<de>
<![CDATA[Das Ziel dieses Mods ist es, das Spiel realistischer zu machen und
das Anpassen des Fahrzeugs für die Aufgabe lohnender.
Das Ziel ist es, den Mod universell zu machen.
Dieser Mod unterstützt Multiplayer und dedizierte Server.
Es sind keine XML-Änderungen erforderlich. Einige Daten aus XML werden überschrieben!

Die Zugkraft für Pflüge, Grubber, Walzen- und Sämaschinen wird von Bodenart und Bodenbeschaffenheit beeinflusst.
Ballenpressen, Ladewagen und Erntemaschinen verbrauchen Leistung basierend auf Füllgeschwindigkeit und Materialdichte.

Beispielsweise:
- Das Säen direkt in die Stoppel erfordert mehr Kraft als das Säen eines kultivierten Feldes.
- Der Betrieb einer Walze in einem gepflügten Feld erfordert mehr Leistung als ein Saatfeld.
- Das Ernten eines höheren Ertrags erfordert mehr Leistung als ein Feld mit niedrigem Ertrag.
- Leichtere Materialien erfordern weniger Kraft als schwere, Heuballen ist einfacher als Gras.

Die auf gezogene Werkzeuge aufgebrachte Kraft wird nun an der richtigen Stelle aufgebracht.
- Die linke oder rechte Seite kann je nach Bodenart und Zustand auf jeder Seite weniger oder mehr Kraft aufgebracht werden.
- Die Kraft wird auch von den Seiten aufgebracht, um die Anbaugeräte anfälliger dafür zu machen, ihrem eigenen Weg zu folgen.
]]>
</de>
    </description>
	<l10n>
	</l10n>
    <iconFilename>icon_REAimplements.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="REAimplements.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>